<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<GameData>

	<Language_en_US>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_COCOA">
			<Text>Cocoa</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_RESOURCE_COCOA_TEXT">
			<Text>Cocoa is produced from the seeds of the tropical cacao tree, which are fermented, roasted, peeled, and then ground into cocoa mass or liquified into chocolate liquor. This pure chocolate was used originally in Mesoamerica, both as a beverage and as an ingredient in foods, and played a special role in both Maya and Aztec royal and religious events. Eventually, once Europeans obtained this luxury, they sweetened and fattened it to create the types of chocolate we know today.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_COFFEE">
			<Text>Coffee</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_RESOURCE_COFFEE_TEXT">
			<Text>Coffee is a brewed beverage prepared from the roasted seeds of several species of evergreen shrub belonging to the genus Coffea. The earliest credible evidence of either coffee drinking or knowledge of the coffee tree appears in the middle of the 15th century, in the monasteries of Arabia. It was there that coffee seeds were first roasted and brewed, in a similar way to how it is prepared today. Eventually, through trade, coffee spread to Venetian ports in Italy, and from there, it was introduced to the rest of Europe.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_TEA">
			<Text>Tea</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_RESOURCE_TEA_TEXT">
			<Text>Tea is an aromatic beverage commonly prepared by pouring hot water over cured leaves of the tea plant. Tea drinking likely began in China, during the Shang Dynasty, when it was initially used for medicinal purposes and combined with other herbs. It was first introduced to Portuguese priests and merchants in China during the 16th century, and later became popular in Britain during the 17th century, which eventually led to Britain competing with China's monopoly over it.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_TOBACCO">
			<!-- WoTMod Text Alteration -->
			<!--<Text>Tobacco</Text>-->
			<Text>Tabac</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_RESOURCE_TOBACCO_TEXT">
			<!-- WoTMod Text Alteration -->
			<!--<Text>Tobacco is a product processed from the dried leaves of plants in the genus Nicotiana. It is used recreationally in cigars and cigarettes, snuff, pipe tobacco, chewing tobacco and flavored shisha. Many Native American tribes have traditionally grown and used tobacco, with some cultivation sites in Mexico dating back to 1400-1000 B.C. Eastern North American tribes carried large amounts of tobacco in pouches as a readily accepted trade item, and often smoked it in peace pipes, either in defined sacred ceremonies or to seal a bargain. Following the arrival of the Europeans, tobacco became increasingly popular as a trade item and grew into its own industry.</Text>-->
			<Text>[TOWRITE] tabac pedia</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_AMBER">
			<Text>Amber</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_RESOURCE_AMBER_TEXT">
			<Text>Amber is fossilized tree resin, which has been appreciated for its color and natural beauty since Neolithic times. Much valued from antiquity to the present as a gemstone, amber is made into a variety of decorative objects. Amber is used as an ingredient in perfumes, as a healing agent in folk medicine, and as jewelry. Because it originates as a soft, sticky tree resin, amber sometimes contains animal and plant material as inclusions.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_JADE">
			<Text>Jade</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_RESOURCE_JADE_TEXT">
			<Text>Jade is an ornamental stone and is the name given to two types of metamorphic rock, nephrite and jadeite. Among the earliest known jade artifacts excavated from prehistoric sites are simple ornaments with bead, button, and tubular shapes. Additionally, jade was used for adze heads, knives, and other weapons, which can be delicately shaped. As metal-working technologies became available, the beauty of jade made it valuable for ornaments and decorative objects. In Chinese history, Jade was considered the "imperial gem" and  had a status-value exceeding that of gold or silver.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_OLIVE">
			<Text>Olives</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_RESOURCE_OLIVE_TEXT">
			<!-- WoTMod Text Alteration -->
			<!--<Text>The olive is a species of small tree in the family Oleaceae, native to the coastal areas of the eastern Mediterranean Basin as well as northern Iraq, and northern Iran at the south of the Caspian Sea. Its fruit, also called the olive, is of major agricultural importance in the Mediterranean region as the source of olive oil. The olive has been the symbol of peace, wisdom, glory, fertility, power and purity. Olive oil has long been considered sacred, and even today,  it is still used in many religious ceremonies. Over the years, the olive has been the symbol of peace, wisdom, glory, fertility, power and purity.</Text>-->
			<Text>[TOWRITE] olives pedia</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_RESOURCE_EBONY">
			<Text>Ebony</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_RESOURCE_EBONY_TEXT">
			<Text>Ebony is a dense black wood, most commonly yielded by several species in the genus Diospyros. It is a very strong wood and is dense enough to sink in water. Its fine texture and very smooth finish when polished, make it valuable as an ornamental wood. Ebony has a long history of use, with carved pieces having been found in Ancient Egyptian tombs. Traditionally, the black pieces in chess sets were made from ebony, with ivory being used for the white pieces. Modern uses are largely restricted to small items, especially musical instrument parts.</Text>
		</Row>
	</Language_en_US>
  
</GameData>