<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Created by ModBuddy on 8/11/2013 9:41:03 PM -->
<GameData>
	<Language_en_US>
		<!-- Unit: Galleon Fleet -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_GALLEON_FLEET">
			<Text>Galleon Fleet</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIVILOPEDIA_UNITS_RENAISSANCE_GALLEON_FLEET_TEXT">
			<Text>[TOWRITE] Galleon Fleet pedia</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_GALLEON_FLEET_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Galleon Fleet is effective against other naval units, allowing fewer defenders to hold off a large naval invasion.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_HELP_GALLEON_FLEET">
			<Text>Unique to Svesta, the Galleon Fleet provides an advantage when fighting other navies. It can also carry more supplies than a standard Frigate, allowing it to effect repairs in foreign waters.</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Unit: Preacher -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_CYAT_PREACHER">
			<Text>Preacher</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_CYAT_PREACHER_TEXT">
			<Text>[TOWRITE] Preacher pedia entry</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_CYAT_PREACHER_STRATEGY">
			<Text>Preachers are slower moving, more powerful missionaries that do not suffer from attrition. Use them to maintain dominance over a foreign city and then capture it using the Cyats' unique ability.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_HELP_CYAT_PREACHER">
			<Text>Powerful missionary replacement.</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Unit: Devout -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_CYAT_DEVOUT">
			<Text>Devout</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_ANTIQUITY_CYAT_DEVOUT_TEXT">
			<Text>[TOWRITE] Devout pedia entry</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_CYAT_DEVOUT_STRATEGY">
			<Text>Devout spawn Preachers whenever they kill an enemy unit. Use this ability to flood your opponents with religious influence.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_HELP_CYAT_DEVOUT">
			<Text>The Preachers spawned by Devout are vulnerable in combat zones. Ensure they fall back quickly.</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Unit: Conscripted Raker -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_NEMYD_CONSCRIPTED_RAKER">
			<Text>Conscripted Raker</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_NEMYD_CONSCRIPTED_RAKER_TEXT">
			<Text>[TOWRITE] Conscripted Raker pedia</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_NEMYD_CONSCRIPTED_RAKER_STRATEGY">
			<Text>Conscripted Rakers are cheap to build and multiply as you plunder opposing trade routes. Keep the pressure on and your opponent will be buried under levied hulls.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_HELP_NEMYD_CONSCRIPTED_RAKER">
			<Text>The backbone of the Numydian navy, Conscripted Rakers have become the bane of Svestan sailors.</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- Unit: Raiders -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ARGAST_RAIDERS">
			<Text>Raiders</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_HELP_ARGAST_RAIDERS">
			<Text>Stronger and more mobile than the spearman, which they replace, Raiders inflict 10 damage to any enemy unit that ends its turn in an adjacent hex.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_ARGAST_RAIDERS_STRATEGY">
			<Text>Raiders are fantastically positioned to move around enemy forces, using their boosted movement to cover ground quickly while their damaging ability fends off units diverted to stop them. Alternatively, station Raiders next to a city to damage its defenders, forcing them to stop to heal or be slowly destroyed.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_ANTIQUITY_ARGAST_RAIDERS_TEXT">
			<Text>[TOWRITE] Raiders pedia</Text>
		</Row>
	</Language_en_US>
</GameData>